<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LIKHA</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="ALLinone">Allow Likha to access following permissions : \n \u0020 \n
        <b>Photos/Media/Files</b> \n \u0020 \u2022 read the contents of your USB storage \n \u0020 \u2022 modify or delete the contents of your USB storage \n\u0020 \n
    </string>
    <string name="str_img1">
        The most well-known face amongst Indian women entrepreneurs -Indra Nooyi is the CFO and President of PepsiCo. \n\n
        With a Masters Degree in Public Management from Yale University and Masters in Finance and Marketing from IIM,
        Kolkata, Nooyi held several senior positions at Motorola and Asea Brown Boveri before joining PepsiCo. \n\n
        Born in Chennai, Indra did her Bachelor’s in Science from Madras Christian College in 1974 . \n\n
        Beginning her career in India, Nooyi held product manager positions at Johnson and Johnson and textile firm Mettur Beardsell.
        Nooyi joined PepsiCo in 1994 and was named president and CFO in 2001.
        She has been conferred with prestigious Padma Bhushan for her business achievements and being an inspiration to India’s corporate leadership. \n\n
        Her strong acumen for business has helped the company garner as much as 30 billion dollars worth of crucial deals within the last couple of years. \n\n

    </string>

    <string name="startup">
        "The critical ingredient is getting off your butt and doing something. It is as simple as that. A lot of people have ideas, but there are few who decide to do something about them now. Not tomorrow. Not next week. But today. The true entrepreneur is a doer, not a dreamer." \n
    </string>


    <string name="category">Select Category</string>
    <string name="title_activity_discover_">Discover</string>
</resources>
